Contact

caitlinkyle0753@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/caitlin-kyle-a0a19792 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills ACLS ICU BLS

Caitlin Kyle

MSN, APRN, FNP-C, CCRN

Dallas, Texas

Summary

Recently graduated from Texas Tech University with a Master of Nursing degree - Family Nurse Practitioner. Now working as an FNP for Urgent Surgery Associates (URSA). Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Patient Education, Intensive Care, Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), Mechanical Circulatory Support Devices. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor of Science (BS) in Nursing from Baylor University Louise Herrington School of Nursing. Certifications in Critical Care and Cardiac Surgery Nursing.

Experience

Urgent Surgical Associates Nurse Practitioner 2020 - Present (less than a year) Dallas, Texas

Baylor University Medical Center Registered Nurse January 2014 - Present (6 years 6 months) Dallas, Texas

Cardiothoracic Intensive Care Unit

Parkland Health and Hospital System
Patient Care Technician
January 2013 - November 2013 (11 months)

Education

Texas Tech University Health Sciences Center

Master of Science in Nursing, Family Nurse Practitioner (2015 - 2019)

Baylor University Louise Herrington School of Nursing Bachelor of Science (BS), Nursing · (2009 - 2013)